<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Firman Aonillah</title>
    <link>https://aonillah21.github.io/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Firman Aonillah</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 10:41:19 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://aonillah21.github.io/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Working Report</title>
      <link>https://aonillah21.github.io/projects/working-report-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 10:41:19 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aonillah21.github.io/projects/working-report-project/</guid>
      <description>Working report is an application to collect information about the work of all employees at PT Padepokan Tujuh Sembilan. The main purpose of this working report application is to monitor the monthly work activities of employees so that it can be seen whether the employee is eligible for a salary for that month.
In the development of this application, I contribute as a technical leader at the front end by preparing a project framework from the project directory, the library that will be used, as well as helping with bug fixing when it&amp;rsquo;s finished loading.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IO Project</title>
      <link>https://aonillah21.github.io/projects/io-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 10:41:19 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aonillah21.github.io/projects/io-project/</guid>
      <description>IO-Project is an e-learning application that is used by employees of PT Padepokan Tujuh Sembilan to improve their knowledge and skills in programming. This application is also used for bootcamp activities for new talents joining PT Padepokan Tujuh Sembilan.
In the development of this application, I contribute as a technical leader at the front end by preparing a project framework, the project directory, the library that will be used, as well as helping with development during the sprint.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jubelio Chat</title>
      <link>https://aonillah21.github.io/projects/jubelio/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 10:41:19 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aonillah21.github.io/projects/jubelio/</guid>
      <description>Jubelio chat is a chat application aimed for online store sellers, making it easier for sellers to reply chats from customers because chat in various e-commerce can be done in just one app, namely jubelio chat. Examples of e-commerce that can be integrated with jubelio chat are like: Shopee, Tokopedia, Bukalapak, Blibli and Lazada.
Work on the jubelio chat aggregator project is done in a team, and our team specifically works on the frontend.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>